<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Call me Frank</title>
    <link>https://sanofrank.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Call me Frank</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 12:53:33 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sanofrank.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fitting Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://sanofrank.github.io/portfolio/fitting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 16:57:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sanofrank.github.io/portfolio/fitting/</guid>
      <description>Automatic application of typographical constraints for printing text documents on browsers Thesis project for my bachelor degree.
Developing of a fitting algorithm which help choosing a paginated sequence with a system of scores, established by typesetting rules (ex. no widows or orphans, no flyspeck, no blank space), that will be then displayed on the browser using the open source framework Paged.js.
 Skills used
 Languages: Javascript, HTML5, CSS3 Concepts: Pagination, Digital Publishing, Typography Tools: Paged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Frank</title>
      <link>https://sanofrank.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 12:53:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sanofrank.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Francesco Paolucci and I’m a computer scientis from Perugia, Italy. I recently graduated from the University of Bologna on the master course called &amp;ldquo;Software Technics&amp;rdquo;, an overtour on the most common latest technologies (machine learning, scalable programming, AI). I have lived in Bologna for the last four years and now I moved back to my hometown.
Working on my thesis I have discovered a big passion about Digital Publbishing and Typography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human2Simpson</title>
      <link>https://sanofrank.github.io/portfolio/human2simpson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 15:35:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sanofrank.github.io/portfolio/human2simpson/</guid>
      <description>Unpaired image to image traslation based on GAN networks. Project done for the Machine Learning exam.
The project is based on CycleGAN model that allows to learn how to transform an image from one domain (style) to an another using for the training two unpaired dataset. Some additions have been made on the traditional CycleGAN.
The aim of the project was in to be able to transform an human face to a simpson version of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Hashtag Recommender System</title>
      <link>https://sanofrank.github.io/portfolio/hashtagrec/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 15:35:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sanofrank.github.io/portfolio/hashtagrec/</guid>
      <description>Hashtag Recommender System based on k-means clustering A hashtag recommender system based on k-means, mini-batch fast k-means and a deep learning feature extraction phase.
The tool developed is a command line interface that takes as input an image and returns a list of hashtags recomandations.
The model built was trained on real data taken from Instagram, for the clustering phase Apache Spark was used for performance reasons.
For possible evaluation you can check the GitHub repository.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>